Tell us about a time when you were learning something new and
Conte-nos de uma vez em que aprendeu algo novo
you had to struggle.
e teve dificuldades.
&gt;&gt; Okay, Katherine, if you're going to ask our students to share
Então, Katherine, se pedir aos alunos que compartilhem
their vulnerable stories on the Internet.
suas histórias vulneráveis na internet.
&gt;&gt; Yeah. &gt;&gt; We have to lead by example.
- Sim. - Temos que dar o exemplo.
&gt;&gt; Okay, fair enough.
Tudo bem, mais que justo.
You go first.
Pode começar.
&gt;&gt; Okay. [LAUGH] Well I've been
Tudo bem.
learning to play the piano for about eight months.
Comecei a aprender a tocar piano há oito meses.
&gt;&gt; Oh okay.
Sim.
&gt;&gt; And the toughest bits for me have been getting one hand right and
E o mais difícil pra mim foi tocar direito em uma mão,
then getting the right hand right and then putting those two things together.
tocar direito na mão direita e depois juntar tudo.
But, when it comes out just so beautiful its like [SOUND].
Mas quando o som sai, soa tão bonito.
&gt;&gt; Oh, that sounds really good.
Parece ser muito bom.
&gt;&gt; I've been playing with my friends, it's really fun.
Eu toco com meus amigos, é muito divertido.
&gt;&gt; Wait, you haven't played for me.
Espera aí, você não tocou pra mim.
&gt;&gt; Well, we'll see if we stay friends till the end of this course
Bem, veremos se vamos ser amigos até o final deste curso.
&gt;&gt; Okay, then.
Então tá.
&gt;&gt; Your turn.
Sua vez.
&gt;&gt; I've struggled with learning Chinese my whole life.
Tive dificuldades em aprender chinês a vida inteira.
&gt;&gt; Wait, you speak Chinese?
Você fala chinês?
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
Sim.
[FOREIGN] &gt;&gt; Wow.
- [CHINÊS] - Nossa!
&gt;&gt; It's no big deal.
Não é nada demais.
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; So, I think the hardest part of
- [RISOS] - Então, acho que o mais difícil
learning Chinese has been trying to learn all the vocab words and
em aprender chinês é aprender todo o vocabulário
trying to put them together in complete sentences without tripping up.
e juntar as palavras em frases completas sem errar.
&gt;&gt; You know this story of yours is reminding me that
A sua história me fez pensar
learning how to make an Android app is like learning a new language.
que aprender a fazer uma aplicativo de Android é como aprender uma língua.
Okay, I could see that.
Entendo.
&gt;&gt; So, you're learning a new vocabulary, and you're putting those things
Estamos aprendendo um novo vocabulário, estamos juntando tudo,
&gt;&gt; Mm-hm.
Aham.
&gt;&gt; Okay, well those are our stories.
Sim, bem estas são nossas histórias.
Now I want our students to share their vulnerable stories.
Agora quero que nossos alunos compartilhem as deles.
Tell us about a time when you learned something new and it was a struggle.
Conte-nos de uma vez em que aprendeu algo